<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MX5 KITT on Robbi Blechdose&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://robbi-blechdose.github.io/mx5kitt/</link>
    <description>Recent content in MX5 KITT on Robbi Blechdose&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 14:27:01 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robbi-blechdose.github.io/mx5kitt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MX-5 KITT: Instrument Cluster</title>
      <link>https://robbi-blechdose.github.io/mx5kitt/03_instrument_cluster/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robbi-blechdose.github.io/mx5kitt/03_instrument_cluster/</guid>
      <description>Arguably, one of the most recognizable parts of KITT is the retro-futuristic dashboard.
As such, my MX-5 KITT had to have one too! However, I shrunk the project to just the instrument cluster. This meant that getting it TÜV approved would be possible, and the amount of work would be manageable.
First order of business was to sketch out what I wanted to have. I eyeballed (pretty badly, admittedly) the shape of the cluster and started drawing: The first and the last sketchNow that I knew what I wanted, it was time to order some parts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MX-5 KITT: Center console</title>
      <link>https://robbi-blechdose.github.io/mx5kitt/02_center_console/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robbi-blechdose.github.io/mx5kitt/02_center_console/</guid>
      <description>In order to give the car a bit more of the sweet 80s retro-futurism vibes, I started work on a new center console piece.
Normally, there is an unused spot between the shifter and the power window switches (well, it contains and ashtray, but that is essentially unused space). I decided to design an inset which would replace the ashtray.
The idea was to add controls for a scanner and a few other useful bits and bobs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MX-5 KITT: Central locking</title>
      <link>https://robbi-blechdose.github.io/mx5kitt/01_central_locking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robbi-blechdose.github.io/mx5kitt/01_central_locking/</guid>
      <description>As the MX-5 will be my daily driver, there are a few convenience mods I&amp;rsquo;m planning. Chief among these is a feature so standard on modern cars noone pays any attention to it: remote central locking.
Even though the MX-5 only has two doors, it&amp;rsquo;s still unnerving to have to use the key on both doors every time, and popping the trunk with the key gets old fast when you go shopping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MX-5 KITT: Introduction</title>
      <link>https://robbi-blechdose.github.io/mx5kitt/00_intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robbi-blechdose.github.io/mx5kitt/00_intro/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I bought a project car: A 1997 Mazda MX-5. It&amp;rsquo;s actually even a special edition called &amp;ldquo;MX-5 Classic&amp;rdquo;. It&amp;rsquo;s got all the latest (well, for 20 years ago anyway) things you&amp;rsquo;d want to have: ABS, double airbags, and luckily not much else. It&amp;rsquo;s a relatively simple car and thus great for modding!
It was only a short drive away, and after initial inspection with my friend Idefix, I immediately picked it up.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
