<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Robbi Blechdose&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://robbi-blechdose.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Robbi Blechdose&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robbi-blechdose.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>K12 KITT: The Scanner</title>
      <link>https://robbi-blechdose.github.io/post/2020-04-27-k12-kitt-scanner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 20:44:22 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robbi-blechdose.github.io/post/2020-04-27-k12-kitt-scanner/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve (probably) been watching way too much Knight Rider recently. As a result, I&amp;rsquo;ve started modifying my car. \
It&amp;rsquo;s by no means a KITT, or even a Trans Am. In fact, it&amp;rsquo;s a Nissan Micra K12.
The first thing I did was add the famous scanner: \
The micra has a handy little space between the hood and the front bumper, perfect for a scanner. The problem is that that space is everything but big.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GameBoy Color Game &#34;Robbi&#34;</title>
      <link>https://robbi-blechdose.github.io/post/2020-02-22-gbc-robbi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 11:25:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robbi-blechdose.github.io/post/2020-02-22-gbc-robbi/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Robbi&amp;rdquo; is a game I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on for a while now. It&amp;rsquo;s written in raw assembly for the GameBoy Color. Though it&amp;rsquo;s currently running on an emulator for easy development, it would run on real hardware as well.
Right now, there isn&amp;rsquo;t much in terms of content as I&amp;rsquo;m still creating the basic systems. However, a few basics are done: \
You can walk (or rather drive) around the map, which has a maximum size of 128x128 tiles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Car Gauge Unit: Graph Mode</title>
      <link>https://robbi-blechdose.github.io/post/2020-01-12-car-gauge-unit-graphmode/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robbi-blechdose.github.io/post/2020-01-12-car-gauge-unit-graphmode/</guid>
      <description>Car Gauge Unit: Graph Mode The small screen at the right-hand side of the unit allows me to enter some data whenever I fill up the tank of my car:
 The amount of fuel I put in (in litres) How much the fuel cost (in € per litre) The total mileage of the car  With this, it calculates the gas mileage (in litres / 100km). However, I only had a total average as well as a &amp;ldquo;best ever&amp;rdquo; value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GB-J Compiler released</title>
      <link>https://robbi-blechdose.github.io/post/2019-10-27-03-gb-j-compiler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 22:05:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robbi-blechdose.github.io/post/2019-10-27-03-gb-j-compiler/</guid>
      <description>GB-J Compiler released! A compiler for a custom Java- and C-like language targeting the GameBoy  This is a project I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on for quite a while, and I&amp;rsquo;d like to continue doing so in the future.
It started out as a school project for my A-levels: Write a compiler.
Choosing the target  The original idea was to target some fantasy computer to reduce the complexity of the project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Car Gauge Unit</title>
      <link>https://robbi-blechdose.github.io/post/2019-10-27-02-car-gauge-unit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 14:29:34 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robbi-blechdose.github.io/post/2019-10-27-02-car-gauge-unit/</guid>
      <description>Car Gauge Unit A project involving Arduino, 3D-Printing and my car This project requires a bit of background information: My car has two standard DIN slots.
The lower one is used up by the car radio, but the upper one just contained a laughably small second glovebox.
Then suddenly, I had an idea: My car is too old to calculate its gas mileage itself, so I might as well add in a device capable of doing that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Blog! 🎉</title>
      <link>https://robbi-blechdose.github.io/post/2019-10-27-01-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 13:52:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robbi-blechdose.github.io/post/2019-10-27-01-first-post/</guid>
      <description>New Blog! 🎉 This is the new blog I&amp;rsquo;ll be using from now on. It&amp;rsquo;ll include posts on all kinds of topics, including (but not limited to):
  Gamedev (for the GameBoy)
  Gamedev (for PC)
  Miscellaneous Arduino and 3D-Printing projects
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
